(wind blowing) The only reason I'm
qualified to give this message to
you
is because of my experience. Hey,
my name's Burt. I have been
involved in technology since 1992.
And what? (Burt chuckles) I've been
in technology since 1992, and I can
tell you this.
What I saw back then is the same
thing that's happening now with AI.
We have about five years
until everything really changes
hard. It's going to take about that
long
for it to really saturate our
systems. So if you are not on the
AI train yet, now is the time.
It is just like 1998 before the
dot-com bust of '99. Everybody's
investing.
Everybody's going gangbusters. But
within eight years of that, 'cause
it took a little longer,
you had social media and
smartphones, and then the whole
fucking world is different after
that.
(Burt sniffles) (birds chirping) My
message is this. History is
repeating itself,
tuk-tuk, logically. (Burt sniffles)
And, what you need to do is be able
to
anticipate the shift as best you
can. And by that, I do something
which I call
future-proofing. And by future-
proofing, what do I mean? I'm not a
fucking swami,
so I can't read a crystal ball and
tell you what is literally going to
happen.
But I can say this. If you look at
the technology at your disposal at
any given moment,
and you know what things have
connect, you can connect and what
things you can't.
And within those things, you kind
of know what's coming next, right?
Every technology has a, oh, new
version coming, right?
Back in the early days of the web,
it was easy to keep track of things
because there wasn't that many
things moving.
There was, you know, if there was
100 things, I'd be surprised. It's
literally millions of small
companies now
changing the earth. And the
acceleration of change is, hasn't
even hit everybody yet.
I see it because I work with the AI
every day, you know? (wind blowing)
I see what it does every day. And
I've used it for enough years now
that I see
the progress it's made just during
my time of using it, let alone how
far it's come
since it's been in the commercial
space, like just for people to use.
And now that I am using it
in pretty much all facets of my
work. And since I'm using it at
that level now,
I see just how valuable and
indispensable it is. And I'm
finding myself to be someone
who is at an interesting point in
AI adoption. I am someone well-
versed in the technology.
Because of my experience, basically
know what to look out for, what to
prepare for,
kind of where things are gonna go.
I do have a general sense. You
know, 100,000 foot view,
what's probably gonna roll out or
what will happen, who the players
are, who the specifics, no fucking
clue.
But I'm pretty sure certain things
will happen. It's kind of like
reading the tea leaves
from a million feet in the sky.
It's, I guess, an intuition thing.
And there's one aspect of having
that kind of intuition,
and it's basically never let me
down. And there have been big times
during my life
where I have doubted it, and you
know, doubted my intuition. And I
either missed out or paid for it.
So I get all kinds of reminders all
the time. Trust your intuition,
trust your intuition.
So Newbert intuition is a big part
of my scheme. My structure, my
backbone infrastructure,
which I'm gonna call it, okay, I'm
tired. That's the end of this
recording.
I think I got something here worth
writing about.